{
  "users": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "fname": "Mahmoud",
      "lname": "Saad",
      "userName": "Mahmoud Saad",
      "password": "Sa3d123",
      "email": "mahmoud.s3d97@gmail.com",
      "role": "admin"
    },
    {
      "fname": "Mahmoud",
      "lname": "Saad",
      "userName": "Msa3d12",
      "email": "srofox20@gmail.com",
      "password": "Thesunmoon123",
      "role": "user",
      "id": 2,
      "exams": [
        {
          "exam": "Js",
          "grade": "100%",
          "date": "6/23/2023"
        },
        {
          "exam": "C#",
          "grade": "100%",
          "date": "6/23/2023"
        },
        {
          "exam": "JavaScript",
          "grade": "40%",
          "date": "6/25/2023"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "fname": "Ahmed",
      "lname": "Osama",
      "userName": "Ahmed12",
      "email": "ss@ss.ss",
      "password": "Ahmed123",
      "role": "user",
      "id": 3,
      "exams": []
    },
    {
      "fname": "Mohamed",
      "lname": "Hamdi",
      "userName": "MHamdi",
      "email": "mohamedHamdi@gmail.com",
      "password": "Mohamed123#",
      "role": "user",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "Exams": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "examName": "JavaScript",
      "Questions": [
        {
          "question": "Javascript is an ___ language?",
          "a": "OOP",
          "b": "Object_Base",
          "c": "procedural",
          "d": "None of the above",
          "correct": "A"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
          "a": "var",
          "b": "let",
          "c": "Both A and B",
          "d": "None of the above",
          "correct": "C"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript",
          "a": "getElementByID()",
          "b": "getElemnetByClassName()",
          "c": "Both A and B",
          "d": "None of the above",
          "correct": "C"
        },
        {
          "question": "Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do?",
          "a": "Throw an Error",
          "b": "Ignors the statements",
          "c": "Gaves a warning",
          "d": "None of the above",
          "correct": "B"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
          "a": "documetn.write()",
          "b": "console.log()",
          "c": "window.alert()",
          "d": "All of the above",
          "correct": "D"
        },
        {
          "question": "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
          "a": "const",
          "b": "let",
          "c": "var",
          "d": "constant",
          "correct": "A"
        },
        {
          "question": "What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
          "a": "in",
          "b": "is in",
          "c": "exist",
          "d": "lies",
          "correct": "A"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the use of the <noscript> tag in Javascript?",
          "a": "The Contents by non-JS based browser",
          "b": "clear all the cookies and cache",
          "c": "Both A and B",
          "d": "Noneof the above",
          "correct": "A"
        },
        {
          "question": "When an operator’s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
          "a": "boolean",
          "b": "undefined",
          "c": "object",
          "d": "integer",
          "correct": "C"
        },
        {
          "question": "What does the Javascript “debugger” statement do?",
          "a": "it will debug all the errors in the program at run time",
          "b": "at act as a breakpoint in a program",
          "c": "it will debug error in the current statement if any",
          "d": "All of the above",
          "correct": "B"
        },
        {
          "question": "What does the ‘toLocateString()’ method do in JS?",
          "a": "return localised object representation",
          "b": "return a parsed string",
          "c": "return localised string representation of an object",
          "d": "none of the above",
          "correct": "C"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
          "a": "stringfy()",
          "b": "parse()",
          "c": "convert()",
          "d": "none of the above",
          "correct": "A"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which of the following are closures in Javascript?",
          "a": "variables",
          "b": "functions",
          "c": "objects",
          "d": "all of the above",
          "correct": "D"
        },
        {
          "question": "What keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in Javascript?",
          "a": "async",
          "b": "await",
          "c": "setTimeout",
          "d": "none of the above",
          "correct": "A"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which of the following are not server-side Javascript objects?",
          "a": "date",
          "b": "fille upload",
          "c": "function",
          "d": "All of the above",
          "correct": "D"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "examName": "C#",
      "Questions": []
    },
    {
      "examName": "sdsfd",
      "Questions": [],
      "id": 4
    }
  ]
}